### GARRETT STEIN-SEROUSSI

Hillsborough, NC 27278

Phone: 919-928-6354 | Email: gsteinseroussi@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/garrettstein-seroussi/ | GitHub: github.com/gsteinseroussi | Portfolio: https://gsteinseroussi.github.io/Portfolio-Page

#### SUMMARY

Enthusiastic full-stack web developer eager to contribute to team success through hard work, attention to detail and excellent organizational skills. Clear understanding of front and back end development. Having spent many years working in various different fields, now motivated to learn, grow and excel. Proficient in Spanish and conversational in Arabic.

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: HTML, JavaScript, CSS

Applications: Node JS, Express, Express-Handlebars, JQuery, Sequelize, MySQL, React,

Bootstrap, AJAX

#### **PROJECTS**

# Bird Tracker | <a href="https://github.com/gsteinseroussi/Bird-Tracker">https://github.com/gsteinseroussi/Bird-Tracker</a> | <a href="https://birdtracker.herokuapp.com">https://birdtracker.herokuapp.com</a>

- An app for bird watching enthusiasts to show other bird watchers what they spotted.
- Created the basic html & handlebar pages, set up the api and html routes, as well as the javascript functionality to add to the database.
- Used HTML, Express-Handlebars, JQuery, Sequelize, CSS, Bootstrap, AJAX

## Hourly Workday Scheduler | <a href="https://github.com/gsteinseroussi/Workday-Scheduler">https://gsteinseroussi.github.io/Workday-Scheduler</a> | <a href="https://gsteinseroussi.github.io/Workday-Scheduler">https://gsteinseroussi.github.io/Workday-Scheduler</a> |

- An hourly scheduler to better manage your time throughout a 9-5 work day.
- Created the local storage functionality and allowed the app to automatically adjust the display based on the current time.
- Bootstrap & Jquery

# Art via Music | <a href="https://github.com/gsteinseroussi/ArtViaMusic">https://github.com/gsteinseroussi/ArtViaMusic</a> | <a href="https://s-suresh-kumar.github.io/ArtViaMusic/">https://s-suresh-kumar.github.io/ArtViaMusic/</a>

- An app that explores keyword creation by taking a user input song, scanning the lyrics to derive keywords, then calling an image from a separate API that matches those keywords.
- In charge of the Javascript for the api call that retrieves an image from the Harvard Museum API.
- JQuery, Ajax, HTML

#### EXPERIENCE

#### Kennel Assistant

January 2016 – Present

#### The Animal Hospital of Carrboro Boarding Kennel

Carrboro, NC

- Maintained clean and organized boarding areas to promote animal wellbeing.
- Advanced client retention by consistently providing outstanding customer service to both clients and pets.
- Converted boarding requested reservation system to an online, easy to track program.

### Freelance Video Editor Movie Makers Inc.

March 2012 – December 2015

Durham, NC

- Performed post-production work, including assembling raw material, editing sound and sequences and providing final product within time and budget constraints.
- Delivered finished videos under deadline to client satisfaction.

### Student Manager UNC Student Stores

March 2011 – December 2014

Chapel Hill, NC

- Offered hands-on assistance to customers, assessing needs and maintaining current knowledge of consumer preferences.
- Directed employees and trained on methods for handling various aspects of sales, complicated issues and difficult customers.

#### **EDUCATION**

Bootcamp Certificate: UNC Chapel Hill, Chapel Hill, NC

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, Chapel Hill, NC

Completed 90 credits towards a Bachelor's Degree in Communications